<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Kevin O’Leary &#8211; Shark Tank Guide</title>
	<atom:link href="https://shark-tank-guide.mystagingwebsite.com/category/kevin-oleary/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://shark-tank-guide.mystagingwebsite.com</link>
	<description>Some of my favorite Shark Tank products</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:31:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">195127237</site>	<item>
		<title>Cup Board Pro</title>
		<link>https://shark-tank-guide.mystagingwebsite.com/2018/12/cup-board-pro/</link>
					<comments>https://shark-tank-guide.mystagingwebsite.com/2018/12/cup-board-pro/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sharktankguide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Daymond John]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevin O’Leary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lori Greiner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matt Higgins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Season 10]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://shark-tank-guide.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=63</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I have to admit, I got a little emotional during the pitch for Cup Board Pro. Here were three young people promoting a product made by their father. His dream was to pitch his creation on Shark Tank, but passed away just a few months before. Keith Young was a NYC fireman and was one... <div class="link-more"><a href="https://shark-tank-guide.mystagingwebsite.com/2018/12/cup-board-pro/">Read More</a></div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I have to admit, I got a little emotional during the pitch for Cup Board Pro. Here were three young people promoting a product made by their father. His dream was to pitch his creation on Shark Tank, but passed away just a few months before.</p>



<p>Keith Young was a NYC fireman and was one of the first responders during 9/11. Unbeknownst to him, he had developed&nbsp;synovial soft sarcoma, a rare form of cancer caused by his exposure at ground zero. He always loved cooking and had even appeared as a contestant on Chopped and won both times! His love of cooking gave him the idea to create his unique cutting board. “The Cup Board Pro” is made of bamboo and has a cup that attaches to catch all the drippings. The board is angled so the juices from along the groove right into the cup! It’s an ingenious invention.</p>



<p>But the story is even more heartbreaking. Keith invented his product in 2010, but he had to put his idea away and help his wife after she was diagnosed with Breast Cancer. She died in 2012.</p>



<p>So his three brave children went on Shark Tank and even showed their father’s audition tape. All the Sharks were moved and they did something I have ever see before. They asked Keith’s children to leave the tank while they discussed a deal. They decided to all work together and offer $100,000 for a 20% stake in the business and promised to donate all their profits to a charity that helps firefighters affected by 9/11.</p>



<p>You too can <a href="https://amzn.to/2QyOSwh">support Keith Young and the NYFD by purchasing the “Cup Board Pro” from Amazon</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://shark-tank-guide.mystagingwebsite.com/2018/12/cup-board-pro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">63</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
